The clouds adorning the setting sun whispered "It's gonna be your turn next" into my ear
But now that they've grown tired of just killing time I'm sure I'll just be their scapegoat
But I'm the king of my very own world
I can even run on top of water
I'm the egg who can put itself back together again after a fall
And can even go on to become an astronaut
I'm sure if I pick up all the beads that rained from the sky and gather them up
Then one day I'll finally be able to plant a flag which signifies my very own liberty
So I pull on my ripped jeans and fight back the tears the draft brings
I exhale a big gulp of air and then another 'cause I'm a boxer rising up again
You only get one chance to come back from the brink
So pound on that door you painted yourself
The colorful ink disperses into two paths
But you're the one who decides how your flower blooms
Chaos
（二海堂(にかいどう)）アア…　ンンッ…
なぜだ！　解(げ)せぬ！
Why?!
Unbelievable!
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
A Block
Finals
B Block
I clawed my way up to C1, the same as you,
貴様と対局する日を心の支えに—
driven by desperation and thoughts of the day I would play against you!
必死の思いで
同じＣ１に上がったというのに…
Tremble
So why can't we play against each other?
なぜ こうも当たらぬ！
Tremble
Wa-pow!
Are you being shy, Kiriyama?!
さては 臆したか 桐山(きりやま)！
Ugh, so noisy.
（零(れい)）あ〜 うるさい
Brisk walking
Why does he blame me?
（零）なんで そうなるかな？
Brisk walking
We had more matches together at the children's tournaments back in elementary school!
（二海堂）これでは 小学生の
子供将棋大会のころのほうが—
対戦できていたではないか
プロになった意味 全くねえ！
There was no point in becoming a professional!
Now we have no choice but to
これでは本当に
なんとしてでも—
become the winners of the Rookie
Tournament's A Block and B Block,
新人戦のＡブロック
Ｂブロックの勝者として—
決勝戦で当たらんかぎりは
今年１年 全く当たれずに—
and go up against each other in the finals,
otherwise we won't have a single match together this year!
終わってしまうではないか〜！
Brisk walking
Stomp
Don't tell me you're thinking, "The Rookie
Tournament is full of rookies, so this'll be easy."
Brisk walking
まさかとは思うが 桐山
Stomp
Brisk walking
貴様 “新人戦なんて
どうせ新人相手だから”とか—
Brisk walking
Stomp
甘く見て
かかってはいないだろうな？
It may be called the "Rookie Tournament," but don't underestimate it!
新人戦といってもナメてかかるな！
I'm not underestimating it.
ナメてませんし
Katsura Room
He made his move. Kumakura, 9-dan, P*2g.
（記者Ａ）
指しました　隈倉(くまくら)九段 ２七歩です
（柳原(やなぎはら)）ハァ…
Um, Shogi Maestro Yanagihara, at this current point,
（記者Ｂ）え〜っと…
では 現時点で 柳原棋匠(きしょう)は—
宗谷(そうや)名人と隈倉九段
どちらを持ちたいと？
who would you like to support,
Master Souya or Kumakura, 9-dan?
（柳原）うん？　いやぁ…
Well, I don't want to support either of them.
どっちも持ちたくねえな
Be serious, Kiriyama!
（二海堂）
真剣になれ 桐山！　おごりは…
Arrogance leads to self-destruction!
Pardon me.
（零）失礼します
Hey, Kiriyama.
（三角(みすみ)）よう 桐山
（松本(まつもと)）ウッス
Yo.
Yes, you're arrogant!
（柳原）まあ
ひと言で言えば混沌(こんとん)かな
If I had to sum it up in one word, it would be "chaos."
I'd go so far as to say you're both arrogant and pompous!
I don't even know which of them is superior.
どっちが優勢かも
こりゃ 分からん
Where do you get that from?
（記者Ａ）
そこをなんとか…
From everything!
But I need something! A headline for the internet!
The prodigy who turned pro in junior high,
destined to become Master!
ネットに載せないと
いけないんです
Okay, how about, "The Master Tournament's final match is a close contest."
You've been relying on that reputation!
〝名人戦 最終局
熱戦〞だね
But Mr. Yanagihara...
（記者Ｂ）柳原先生…
Ugh, it's so noisy.
あ〜 うるさい
Issa, Smith.
一砂(いっさ) スミス
そいつら つまみ出しちゃって
Throw those two out.
（三角）へい！　がってんだ！
（二海堂）キャッ！
Yep.
At once!
At once.
（松本）押忍(おす)！　今すぐに！
（零）えっ？　僕まで？
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
Right away!
Me too?!
Compact...
Sheesh. That's what I hate about youngsters.
…たく　若いってヤダヤダ
Don't use words to fight. Settle it with shogi.
ケンカは口ですんな
将棋でやれ　…たく
Jeez.
おっと…　宗谷 ３七飛か
Whoa. Souya did R*3g.
Well, it's nice to see some enthusiasm, don't you think?
（棋士Ａ）まあまあ
元気があっていいじゃないですか
I wish they would share a little with their mentor.
ちょっと 兄弟子に
分けてやってほしいくらいですよ
You mean Shimada?
（棋士Ｂ）あ〜 島田(しまだ)さんな
He's been lacking in ambition recently.
最近 覇気がないもんな
なんか迷ってるっつうか—
It's like he's lost or something.
Like, what happened to him, you know?
“どうしちゃったんだろう”
…みたいな
In the Shogi Maestro Tournament qualifiers,
こないだの棋匠戦予選も—
he kept making moves that were unusual for him.
なんか らしくない
手ばっか指してさ
Maybe Souya sucked the soul right out of him?
宗谷さんに—
魂吸われちゃったんじゃ
ねえの？
（棋士Ｂ）なんか影まで
薄くなっちゃってるっていうか
It looks like even his shadow has become lighter, you know?
なあ？
ていうか 薄くなって
きちゃってんのは—
In fact, his shadow's not the only thing that's been thinning out!
影だけじゃ
なかったりして
（棋士Ｂ）ハハハハッ…
（棋士Ａ）おっと…
Whoa, calm down a little!
（後藤(ごとう)）ふ〜ん…
Guys who'll never get close to a
title match are so happy-go-lucky.
（後藤）気楽でいいな
タイトル戦に縁のないヤツは
後藤…
Gotou.
Instead of worrying about another player's mental health,
棋士なら人の頭の心配より—
you should worry about your own life, and the possibility that it could end without ever being in a title match.
タイトル戦にも
出られずに終わるかもしんない—
自分の人生の心配でもしてろよ
Gotou.
（柳原）後藤
That's a bit harsh.
言い過ぎだ
Oh, Kumakura did S*3f.
…と　隈倉が３六銀っと
やっぱりね　来ると思った
Not a surprise. I thought he might do that.
This is also...
これが また…
a good move.
いい手なんだよな
Dammit!
（棋士Ｂ）くそ…
Let it go. Come on.
（棋士Ａ）
いいから 行くぞ
There, you see? They left.
（柳原）ほ〜ら 見ろ
出てっちまったじゃねえか
Who cares? Probably went to the can.
（後藤）知らん　便所じゃね？
What are you going to do about this mood?
どうすんのよ？　この空気
凍りついちゃったじゃないのさ
It's colder than ice in here now. Jeez...
…たく お前は
Everyone who's gotten their butts kicked in a title match will always lose their composure for a bit.
タイトル戦で
吹っ飛ばされた人間はね
皆 一度は調子を崩す
That's just...
それはね…
how it is.
当たり前
"At this rate, I'll just lose."
（柳原）“このまんまじゃ
ダメなんだ”と—
番勝負の間に
徹底的に思い知るからだ
That's what they come to realize in between matches of a series.
They have to break themselves apart,
and then reconstruct it again from the shattered pieces.
そして
自分を１回 バラバラに壊して—
再構築を試みるからだ
They start over from square one.
またイチからな
It's the same for everyone.
（柳原）み〜んな そう
Well, by "everyone,"
I mean players who've experienced that.
まあ “みんな”って
経験したヤツはってことだけどね
フン…　島田なんて どうせ
放っときゃ 勝手に また勝ちだすさ
I'm sure if you leave Shimada alone, he'll just start winning again.
It just disgusts me...
（後藤）俺は ただ…
リングに上がりもしねえで
野次(やじ)だけ飛ばすヤツ見ると—
to see people heckling others when they
haven't even climbed into the ring themselves.
虫酸(むしず)が走るんだよ
ハァ…　そうやって お前は もう…
And so, you're always slashing
up everything like a knife itself.
ナイフみたいに
ギッザギザ ギザギザ
You're always so touchy. What are you, twelve-years-old?
いつまでも とがりやがって
中学生かよ？
Jeez, act like an adult already.
ハン…　もう…
大人になれ 大人に
Gloomy
すみません
Excuse us.
Gloomy
We haven't been in a title match at all.
僕ら まだ タイトル戦
一度も出たことなくて…
Gloomy
So how much time is left?
（後藤）…で 持ち時間は？
こっちが宗谷？
Is this Souya's side?
Sheesh. In one ear and out the other, huh?
…たく　人の話 ホント聞かねえな
Kuma just passed the one-hour mark.
隈が １時間切ったとこ
ふ〜ん…
（香子(きょうこ)）
ねえ 零　どうしよう？　私
Tell me, Rei. What should I do?
I'm...
怖い…
scared.
（零）ハァハァ…
義姉(ねえ)さんに もう近づくな
Stay away from my sister for now on!
自分は結婚してんだろう
なに考えてんだよ？
You're married, aren't you?
What are you thinking?
ハァハァ…　家族を
大切にできないヤツは クズだ！
People who can't cherish their family are trash!
Trash, huh?
“クズ”ね
でもって “許せない”　ふ〜ん…
And also unforgivable?
What are you?
なに？　お前　誰？
Who?
A god?
（後藤）神？
This is good. This is bad.
“これはいい　これはダメ”
全部 お前が決めんの？
Are you the one who decides all that?
I see.
へえ…
I don't know.
（零）分からない　僕には…
To me, humans are the embodiment of chaos.
人間は混沌そのものだ
The person who got mad on Shimada's behalf and the person who makes my sister suffer are living in the same body.
（零）島田さんのために
腹を立てた彼と—
義姉を苦しめる彼は
一個の体に住んでいる
How should I...
そいつを僕は…
Oh, he made a move.
（三角）オッ…　指したぞ
（零）あっ…
（三角）宗谷 ３九歩成
Souya played P-3h+.
What? Does he have time for that?
（柳原）なんだ？
そんなんで間に合うのか？
In that case, respond with B*8c. And then, after that...
なら ８三角と来るとして 次は…
Should I hate him?
（零）憎めばいいのか…
Or...
それとも…
なに？　後藤　帰んの？
What is it, Gotou? You're leaving?
（後藤）あした 対局なんで
I have a match tomorrow.
Don't make Kouda cry too much.
あんまり幸田(こうだ)を泣かしてくれるなよ
Why do you always have this fierce stance?
なんで いつも 仁王立ちなんだ？
Fierce?
（香子）
仁王？　鬼みたいとか言いたいの？
Are you saying I look like an ogre?
So you're already aware of it.
あ〜 自覚あるんだ？
Rage
Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage          Rage
What's wrong, Kiriyama?
（三角）どうした？　桐山
Oh, uh...
あっ いえ…
何でもないです
It's nothing.
For some reason, I suddenly had the feeling she was near.
なぜだか不意に
彼女が そばにいるような気がした
The last time I saw her was in March.
最後に会ったのは３月
I thought about calling her after that,
携帯を鳴らしてみようかと
思ったけれど—
手を伸ばしかけて やめた
but I stopped when I reached for the phone.
What should we even talk about?
何を話せばいい…
Even if she were close to me, the one standing next to her is...
そばにいるのだとしたら
隣にいるのは…
Sometimes it'll look simple to unravel,
but other times it looks messed up and tangled.
簡単に ほどけそうに見えるし—
グチャグチャに
こんがらがっているようにも見える
If I had to put it in one word...
まあ ひと言で言えば…
Then Yanagihara paused for a moment before muttering...
（零）そして 柳原さんは
ひと息置いて ポツリと つぶやいた
"Chaos."
（柳原）混沌だな
Chaos
Kumakura
Day two of the seventh match
of the 69th Master Tournament.
（アナウンサー）
第69期 名人戦　第７局 ２日目
It's been a close contest that has gone the distance,
but this is the final match.
フルセットまで もつれ込む熱戦で
ついに迎えた最終局
It will decide the winner.
ついに 今日で決着がつきます
（アナウンサー）
夕食休憩を挟み—
Because of the dinner break,
both players have less time, but their expressions look calm.
双方 残り時間も
短くなってきましたが—
両名とも 落ち着いた表情です
宗谷名人 連続５期
通算11期の名人防衛なるか
Master Souya has won the title the last five times, totaling 11 wins. Will he retain it today?
連続４回目 挑戦者 隈倉健吾(けんご)九段
タイトル奪取なるか
Or will Kumakura Kengo, 9-dan,
the challenger for the fourth time in a row, seize the title?
Ah, Master Souya has made his move.
（聞き手）
あっ ここで 宗谷名人 指しました
B-4d.
４四角　これは…
This is...
（聞き手）
いかがでしょう？　解説の辻井(つじい)さん
What do you think, commentator Tsujii?
Tsujii, 9-dan
the match's commentary hall
（辻井）ふむ…　これは
意外な一手ですね
This is an unusual move.
Why did he do that?
何だろう？　この手は
It's not B-3g+, nor is it +R-3g.
３七角成でもないし
３七竜でもないし
It feels like he wasted a move.
一手渡したって感じですかね？
It doesn't have any special meaning.
（三角）特に意味はないような…
That's because this is a free-for-all.
混戦ですからね
It's like saying, "Go ahead. Think about this."
“どうぞ そちらが
考えてください”ってことでしょう
It happens.
あるんですよ
I don't think even Souya would know what to do anymore.
なんか きっと
分かんなくなっちゃったんでしょう
宗谷君も
I get it.
分かります
Yes, yes.
Then at this stage, could we say Kumakura, 9-dan, has a slight advantage?
（聞き手）では 現段階では—
隈倉九段が少し有利
…ということに？
ハハッ…　ですね
Bam
Indeed!
I'm sure Kumakura, 9-dan, will do a dodge move next.
隈倉九段
ここは かわす一手でしょう
He'll probably make his move quickly.
すぐ指すと思います
Wait.
待てよ　これは…
This is...
I lost.
（隈倉）負けました
What?
（アナウンサー）
えっ？　あっ…　投了？
Oh, he resigned.
Kumakura, 9-dan, has resigned!
隈倉九段 投了です
宗谷名人 防衛です
Master Souya has defended his title!
（関係者）と… 投了？
R-Resigned?!
Wait a second! So suddenly?
（関係者）えっ？
ちょ まっ…　いきなり？
Hey, get the camera!
（関係者）おい カメラ！
（関係者）立会人も入ってないぞ
The observer isn't even there!
Hello? He resigned!
（関係者）もしもし？　投了です
Hurry!
Where's Nakamura, the observer?
（関係者）
立会人の中村(なかむら)さん どこだ？
（関係者）隈倉 投了
ですから投了です　急いでください
Kumakura resigned.
I said, he resigned!
Please hurry!
Huh? Resigned?
（三角）えっ？　投了？
いきなり ここで？
Just like that?
Why, Kumakura?
隈倉さん なんで？
Wasn't that too soon?
早すぎませんか？　まだ指す手は…
ていうか てっきり優勢だと…
He still had moves he could play.
I mean, I thought he had the upper hand.
No. He was checkmated.
いや 詰んでいる　きっちり17手
In precisely 17 more moves.
Kx1e.
（零）同玉
P-1d.
（二海堂）１四歩
L-1d.
同香
Kx1d.
同玉
It's true.
ホントだ
No one noticed.
誰も気づかなかった
But when it's played out, there's no denying it.
でも 指されてみると 確かに
これ以上 指す手はない
At this point, he was trapped,
no matter how he played.
どう動いても…
It's all in vain.
全て無効！
（柳原）宗谷…
Souya.
（柳原）見事なり
Brilliant.
I didn't train enough.
修練が足りなかった
そのひと言に尽きます
That's all I can say.
また１年 順位戦を戦い抜き—
For this next year, I'll fight off everyone in the class-promotion tournaments
and train hard so I can come back and sit here again.
また ここに座れるよう
鍛錬するのみ
Oh man. He's so cool.
（松本）やべえ　超カッコイイ
く… 隈倉九段 シビれる！
K-Kumakura, 9-dan, gives me goosebumps!
I want to be like him!
俺も こんな風格が欲しい！
How can he be so calm about it?
（三角）どうして
こんな泰然としていられるんだ？
フルセット混戦の そのあとで
Right after seven hotly-contested matches?
Ah, Kengo is so cool!
（三角）あ〜 健吾 かっけえ！
（松本）アア〜…
Is it confidence?
（零）自信か…
Starting over at square one and fighting through Class A,
the den of demons, again and again,
魔物の住みかのＡ級順位戦を
何度でもイチから戦い抜いて—
来年も きっと
目の前に座ってやるという…
swearing that he'll be sitting in front of the champion next year too...
Sorry I took so long.
お待たせ！
Here.
はい　化粧水と乳液と…
Toner, lotion, and they had a new
moisturizing cream, so I tossed that in.
ついでに 新作の保湿クリーム
出てたから 入れといた
I think that should do it.
これで多分 大丈夫よ
Sorry for the hassle.
おう 悪いな
I won't stop sneezing if I go into places like that.
俺は こういうとこに入ると
くしゃみが止まらなくなる
じゃあな　助かった
See you. Thanks again.
Want me to go with you?
ついてったげようか？
I'll thank you properly next time.
（後藤）礼は また今度　じゃ
Later.
中央病院まで
Central Hospital.
（後藤）よう
Hey.
来たぞ　美砂子(みさこ)
I'm here,
Misako.
（後藤）なっ…
（香子）遅〜い！
You're late!
Why are you here?!
なんで いるんだ？
Here. I picked these up for you.
（香子）
はい　取ってきといてあげたわよ
You were collecting too many claim checks.
…ていうか 預かり証 ため込み過ぎ
Claim checks?
“預かり”…　さっきの財布か
From my wallet earlier!
Enough. Get up.
（後藤）もういい　立て
タクシーに放り込んでやる
I'll throw you in a taxi.
Phooey
Forget it. I'm staying over.
（香子）ヤダ　泊まってく
（後藤）ダメだ！
No way. If I did that, you'd definitely attack me.
だって そんなことしたら
お前 絶対 俺のこと襲うもん
*98% Bullseye
A-Attack?
（香子）お… 襲っ…
*98% Bullseye
Shock
I-I wouldn't!
そ… そんなことしないもん！
Blush
Then never mind. I'm leaving!
じゃ もういい
帰ります！　帰るもん！
I'm going home!
Good.
（後藤）おう
Will you walk me to the taxi stand?
（香子）
タクシーのとこまで送ってくれる？
Yeah, sure.
（後藤）ああ いいよ
（香子）あっ…
荷物くらい中に入れといたら？
Why don't you at least put your dry cleaning inside?
（後藤）うん？　あ〜 そうだな
Oh, right.
Gleam
（香子）にゅるん！
（後藤）アッ… アア…
…たく
When all is said and done, your defenses are weak, huh?
（香子）
何だかんだ言って 脇が甘いのよね
That's why I take advantage of you.
だから 私につけ込まれるのよ
Whatever, just go home already. I'm really tired.
（後藤）いいから
もう帰ってくれよ　俺 眠いんだよ
That's okay. Just go to sleep.
（香子）いいわよ 寝て
どうぞ おかまいなく
Pay me no attention.
Fine. You're so troublesome.
（後藤）
あ〜 もういい　面倒くせえ　来い
Come here.
Poof
Shine
What?
（香子）えっ？　ちょ…
な… なに？　これ　ウッ…
Hey, what is this?
Goodnight.
（後藤）おやすみ
（香子）え… ええっ？
Wh-What?!
H-Hey! What is this?! Untie me!
ちょ… ちょっと！　なに これ
ほどきなさいよ　どういうことよ？
How could you?!
My clothes will get wrinkly!
（香子）服 シワになっちゃう！
それに 化粧落とさないと
And I need to get my makeup off!
Hey!
ちょっと！
Roll
Grab
There are deep shadows under his eyes.
（香子）目の下の深い影
He probably hasn't slept well in a long time.
多分 もうずっと
よく眠れてなかったのだろう
His face is pale.
青い顔
Ugh...
もう…　バカ！
Idiot.
Now I can't get mad at you.
怒れないじゃない
Not after you show me this face.
そんな顔 見せられたら…
（零）翌日
The next day,
Kumakura, 9-dan, took the early morning
limited express train and left Hakone behind.
朝イチの特急で 隈倉九段は
ひとり 箱根(はこね)をあとにした
Um, Chairman, excuse me...
（スタッフ）
あの…　会長　ちょっと…
（神宮寺(じんぐうじ)）うん？　何でしょう？
Huh? What is it?
When we entered the room to clean it this morning...
（スタッフ）
今朝 清掃に入りましたら—
Crumble
it was in this state.
このような ありさまでありまして
ホント いかがなものかと…
Ruined
I thought I should show it to you.
（神宮寺）
隈倉〜っ！　あんにゃろう！
Kumakura!
That bastard!
（柳原）アハハハッ…
（神宮寺）笑いごっちゃねえよ！
It's not funny!
I see! So he kicked the hell out of the wall!
（柳原）そうか　壁を蹴破ったか
やるな 隈ちゃん　ハハハハッ…
What a character!
He's definitely going to pay for the damages and get a severe penalty!
（神宮寺）
もちろん 全額弁償 アンド—
ペナルティー
てんこ盛りにしてやる！
I'll send him to shogi events on department store rooftops during the sweltering summer vacation!
灼熱(しゃくねつ)の夏休みの デパートの屋上の
将棋イベントに—
片っ端から送り込んでやる！
To think he would kick a hole in the wall after losing.
（柳原）
しっかし 負けて壁 蹴破るとはね
ハハハハッ…　隈のヤツ
Oh, Kuma.
I get it, though.
（柳原）そうだよな　悔しいよな
It must've been frustrating.
It couldn't have been anything other than frustrating.
悔しくない訳なんて
あるわきゃないよな
Kumakura
I wonder why I'm smiling
The night wears on as I trace it with a finger
In the oversized nooks of this world
My heart continues to melt away
Like the petals of a flower repelling the rain yet refusing to wither
All the things important to me have spilled out
Before I knew it I was all alone and I'd walked a great distance
I'd forgotten what my own voice really sounded like
And it was the strangest feeling
After dawn broke on that long night
I remembered as if it were all a dream
I gave myself up to that nostalgic eternity
And it seems like I can go on walking again
Next Episode Preview
So we've both cleared
our first match, huh?
Episode 25
（二海堂）まずは
お互い 初戦はクリアか
I never realized he had so much hidden passion beneath that calm exterior.
（三角）
あの静けさの裏に—
そんな熱さを
隠していたなんて…
Something that looks refreshing and would go well with cold, green tea...
（あかり）
見た目は涼しげで—
冷たい緑茶に
合うような…
Let's see... A duck?
（モモ）う〜んとね…
アヒルさん！
That brings back a lot of memories.
（有本(ありもと)）
何もかも皆 懐かしい
Illustration: Okazaki Mari
Please watch the next episode of "March comes in like a lion" too.
（隈倉）
「３月のライオン」
次回も よろしく
（神宮寺）隈倉ぁ！
Kumakura!
その前に ちょっと
話があるんだが…
I need to talk to you!